<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business on Matteo Cervelli</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/tags/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business on Matteo Cervelli</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 07:46:49 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localhost:1313/en/tags/business/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Revenue: 5 KPIs that Predict Your Scaling Capability</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/5-kpi-scalability/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 07:46:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/5-kpi-scalability/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you driving your company looking only at the rearview mirror?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Revenue tells you where you have been, not where you are going. Healthy and sustainable companies in the long term monitor indicators that can predict opportunities and risks. Leaders know that long-term success requires a complete vision beyond sales numbers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you want to know which are the key indicators that forward-thinking entrepreneurs monitor?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this article I will show you the dashboard of indicators to constantly update that make the difference between a resilient business and one vulnerable to unforeseen events.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>37, The Year of Descent</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/37-year-of-descent/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/37-year-of-descent/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;37, the year of descent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I blow out 37 candles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This has been the most intense, challenging, and meaningful year of my life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I had to choose one word that best characterizes this year, I choose descent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a year in which I chose to descend. I would have liked to climb back up too, but it feels good to be down as well. And the bottom never ends - the bottom of frustration, the bottom of repressed anger, the bottom of shame, and the bottom of others&amp;rsquo; judgment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Purple Cow</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/the-purple-cow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 09:52:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/the-purple-cow/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This blog post collects my takeaway from the book: &lt;a href=&#34;https://amzn.to/3E4vBx9&#34;&gt;The Purple Cow by Seth Godin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is nothing but an ingredient to be successful: being a Purple Cow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wait, what&amp;rsquo;s a Purple Cow?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Purple Cow is a concept defined by Seth Godin to indicate the extraordinary that allows a business to stand out from the mass and build success. It&amp;rsquo;s not just an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s the necessary choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And, unfortunately, it&amp;rsquo;s not enough.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss> 