<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on Matteo Cervelli</title><link>https://matteocervelli.com/en/categories/about/</link><description>Recent content in About on Matteo Cervelli</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 19:24:29 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matteocervelli.com/en/categories/about/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss"/><item><title>What I'm doing now</title><link>https://matteocervelli.com/en/now/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:12:52 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://matteocervelli.com/en/now/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>Note: this is a &lt;a href="https://nownownow.com">Now&lt;/a> page.&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Updated: 2025-01-18, from my home in Poggibonsi, Tuscany, Italy.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="i-help-companies-grow-in-a-scalable-way">I help companies grow in a scalable way&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>I am a business consultant and advisor.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My work consists of helping companies grow in a scalable way through Strategy, Change Management, Sales and Business Development, Leadership Training and Coaching.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Many of my entrepreneur friends have noticed that I&amp;rsquo;ve switched to the other side of the fence. My strength lies precisely in combining my experience as a family business partner + medium/large company management + international sales with my skills as a Scalability Engineer.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://matteocervelli.com/en/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:26:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://matteocervelli.com/en/about/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="in-short">In short&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m Matteo Cervelli. I am &lt;a href="https://matteocervelli.com/work/business-scalability-engineer">Business Scalability Engineer&lt;/a>. I act as a &lt;a href="https://matteocervelli.com/en/work/">Consultant and Advisor&lt;/a>. Previously I managed &lt;a href="https://www.urania.group">Urania Group&lt;/a> as Co-CEO.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Today I help entrepreneurs and leaders to grow their business, in strategy, management, sales, implementing the principles of scalability.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My purpose is to trigger people to build a more beautiful world, together.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I am a father of 3 little girls, Emma, ​​Maria and Emma, ​​and two dogs: Maple and Cookie. Even before that, I am a husband: Sara and I have known each other since 2005 and in these 20 years we have loved each other and have always been there for each other, one, two and infinite.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>