<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Testimonials on Matteo Cervelli</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/categories/testimonials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Testimonials on Matteo Cervelli</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localhost:1313/en/categories/testimonials/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alberto Rossi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/alberto-rossi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/alberto-rossi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have met many entrepreneurs, many good CEOs and a few extraordinary ones. Matteo has the courage to go further, from a human point of view and from a business vision point of view. He also has the stamina needed day by day to build that vision. It&amp;rsquo;s a pleasure to work with him.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alexia Redini</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/alexia-redini/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/alexia-redini/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had the pleasure of working with Matteo for a long period during which he proved to be exceptionally reliable and focused.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of his greatest qualities is his ability to plan and manage complex projects. His ability to foresee different scenarios and create detailed plans has led to significant improvements in operations and processes within our team. Thanks to his far-sighted perspective and attention to detail, he has generated a significant positive impact on our work, contributing to everyone&amp;rsquo;s growth and the achievement of objectives.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fabrice Pettoello</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/fabrice-pettoello/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/fabrice-pettoello/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Matteo is a figure who embodies curiosity and intellectual energy. His lively gaze reflects a mind that is never satisfied with superficial or banal answers. Always looking for the why of things, Matteo does not limit himself to observing the surface, but immerses himself directly in the essence of the issues to understand how to improve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His attitude towards innovation and change is contagious and inspiring. It&amp;rsquo;s not just about wanting to improve existing processes, but about transforming the entire organizational structure into something beautiful and meaningful. This vision of beauty is not limited to aesthetics, but extends to the beauty of efficient functioning, long-term goal, and the personal and professional growth of the people around him.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Federico Trippi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/federico-trippi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/federico-trippi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Matteo is a person with vision, who does not give up reading beyond the surface. He loves to dare to set himself challenges that are concrete but at the same time above the line of &amp;ldquo;immediately feasible&amp;rdquo;. This attitude can be viral and also allows the people around him to look beyond the immediately achievable results (often of modest value), to set themselves more ambitious and certainly more satisfying goals.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filippo Maone</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/filippo-maone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/filippo-maone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Matteo is a guide who accompanies me towards objectives aimed at personal and work improvement. An ally who taught me to always ask myself stimulating questions, and from their answers I always learned new things. I remember the first day of Kata, with his enthusiasm he involved me in a project that allowed us to overcome challenges that previously seemed like utopias.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In just a few months we have doubled our daily door production, reaching 100 pieces per day. But the thing that made me grow the most was my attitude to change. He gave me the tools, and taught me how to use them, and thanks to this no new role or task scares me, I have been purchasing manager, manager of a production department and delivery manager.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Francesca Sernissi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/francesca-sernissi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/francesca-sernissi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve known Matteo for a few years now, because we attended a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree together at the Universities of Pisa, Florence, Siena and Scuola Superiore Sant&amp;rsquo;Anna&amp;hellip; to learn to climb! By participating in the master&amp;rsquo;s course with Matteo I understood that for him climbing is not just a way to reach the top, but above all THE way to determine an impact in the world that is sustainable (from all points of view, i.e. social, economic and of governance) and therefore be successful in the broadest and noblest sense of the term.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Francesco Ferraro</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/francesco-ferraro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/francesco-ferraro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I met Matteo in the company I work for, he is a very prepared and determined person, Matteo is a mentor, working with him, in addition to being a privilege, is very important: his ability to vision the future combined with external reality, and his way of transmitting it has always been a source of great motivation for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every project, every goal to be achieved, always becomes challenging and at the same time educational. The way in which he structured and made tangible the company&amp;rsquo;s values, which have become our cornerstones, was so engaging that to this day they do not allow us to lose our way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Francesco Lagonigro</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/francesco-lagonigro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/francesco-lagonigro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Matteo is a transparent, curious person, guided by a strong ethic in managing relationships and a strong sense of innovation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gianni Cordaro</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/gianni-cordaro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/gianni-cordaro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Matteo is an amazing professional who helped me to find the best path for my company. And now that&amp;rsquo;s working perfectly. I really recommend him to those entrepreneurs who want to make decisive choices for their businesses and to all those companies who want to embark on a path of innovation and change&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laura Masoni</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/laura-masoni/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/laura-masoni/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Matteo is for me inspiration, support, respect and passion for life. We worked closely together for two years, in which I grew every single day thanks to his contribution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Matteo is inspiration, because he is constantly looking for new methods, tools, points of view and loves to share all his discoveries. In this way he is a source of inspiration, both for new activities or systems to share, and for being curious and open to new things like he is.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luigi Paganelli</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/luigi-paganelli/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/luigi-paganelli/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The first time I had the chance to talk to Matteo I noticed his natural and determined propensity for all types of innovation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, what aroused great interest in me was his idea of organisation, based on creating a structured and internally coherent structure with very clear and long-term objectives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is not just a desire to change to improve the process, both productive and managerial, to be able to make those improvements that make company life more fluid, but to &amp;ldquo;give&amp;rdquo; everyone a concept of company based on &amp;ldquo;beauty&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mattia Guida</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/mattia-guida/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/mattia-guida/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You are a person with an extraordinary learning ability, you can see things that others don&amp;rsquo;t see but that will happen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You travel a lot (mentally) into the future and this sometimes makes you lose contact with the present, perhaps this makes it difficult for you to communicate with other people (difficulty in making yourself understood) but it is precious for boosting activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You care a lot about the human side of people, this does you a lot of credit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michele Lasi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/michele-lasi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/michele-lasi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Matteo is one of the brightest minds I&amp;rsquo;ve ever met.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After our common path at University, Matteo become a sort of personal consultant to get in touch with for sincere and effettive advices when facing the most complex milestone of my career.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His business acumen, paired with his skills from his deep organizational experience and his talent in motivating and leading teams are remarkable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am truly fascinated by Matteo&amp;rsquo;s natural leadership and ability to make things happen. He naturally connects and engages with stakeholders at all levels of an organization by his energetic, positive and easy style.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rossana Gloriosi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/rossana-gloriosi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/rossana-gloriosi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;No matter what the problem is, Matteo dedicates himself completely to it with passion and professionalism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Always reliable, punctual and organised.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Highly recommended!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stefano Boldrini</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/stefano-boldrini/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/testimonials/stefano-boldrini/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Matteo is undoubtedly a person out of the ordinary for the way he is able to think and see certain things and sometimes he doesn&amp;rsquo;t realize this, risking &amp;ldquo;running alone&amp;rdquo; but as far as I&amp;rsquo;m concerned the experience, or rather the opportunity that he gave me and that I would like to tell you about, I believe, represents very well the concept of &amp;ldquo;talent development&amp;rdquo; that he carried out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After having completed a very important training course himself, he decided not to reserve that experience for himself but to share it with me, allowing me to follow the same path, this allowed me to come into contact with people and skills that I would never have imagined and for me this represents a very beautiful and clear form of how to make those around you and in whom you strongly believe grow.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss> 