<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Page on Matteo Cervelli</title><link>https://matteocervelli.com/en/categories/page/</link><description>Recent content in Page on Matteo Cervelli</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 12:53:02 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matteocervelli.com/en/categories/page/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss"/><item><title>AI Usage</title><link>https://matteocervelli.com/en/ai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://matteocervelli.com/en/ai/</guid><description>&lt;p>Updated February 15, 2025.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>LLMs are a tool that has recently been taking up a lot of space in the world, and also in how I approach my work.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Although they are not infallible, using these tools has allowed me to enhance my content creation capabilities and also to write code.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Every piece of content you see produced on the site was originally written by me in at least one of the languages I support, namely Italian and English. For translation, I often rely on an auto-translated first draft. Therefore, it may happen that one of the two languages presents verbal forms generated by an LLM that I haven&amp;rsquo;t completely rewritten, especially in older articles predating February 15, 2025, when I published the new version of the site on Netlify.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Work with me</title><link>https://matteocervelli.com/en/work/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 14:52:50 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://matteocervelli.com/en/work/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="my-value-system">My value system&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="why">Why&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>I unlock people&amp;rsquo;s talent and potential to build a more beautiful world together.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="how">How&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>I help companies grow in a scalable way, to build ecosystems that enable comfort, skills, and overall well-being.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what">What&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>I work as a consultant, advisor, and trainer, as well as making personal investments.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="principles">Principles&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Beauty&lt;/strong> is the key to unleashing creativity and eliminating poverty.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Whether you choose easy or difficult &lt;strong>challenges&lt;/strong>, they require the same energy. Always aim high.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Learning, &lt;strong>failing&lt;/strong>, and trying again are the only ways to grow.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A company&amp;rsquo;s capability is its unique value proposition, its potential lies in the strength of &lt;strong>relationships&lt;/strong> that leadership maintains.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>An evolving business is based on few &lt;strong>experiments&lt;/strong>, but with great potential. And at the same time, many diversified stimuli of mammoth opportunities that simmer quietly.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;a href="#book-now" class="mc-button" id="book-now-button" data-umami-event="Book Now Button Click 1">
 Book now a free session
 &lt;br>
 to talk about your idea
&lt;/a>
&lt;h2 id="services-i-offer">Services I offer&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="management-consulting">Management Consulting&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>My consulting services are customized to &lt;a href="https://matteocervelli.com/en/business-scalability-engineer">unlock your company&amp;rsquo;s potential&lt;/a> and guide you toward success. Working together, we&amp;rsquo;ll transform challenges into opportunities. I can support you with tailored methodologies, strategic vision, insights, and operational excellence.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Unlock your business growth with a Scalability Engineer</title><link>https://matteocervelli.com/en/business-scalability-engineer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 08:41:33 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://matteocervelli.com/en/business-scalability-engineer/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="here-is-why-you-need-a-business-scalability-engineer-to-grow-your-business-the-way-it-deserves">Here is why you need a Business Scalability Engineer to grow your business the way it deserves.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Do you know when a company seems blocked, growth slows down, problems multiply and you don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start to put things back in order?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Here, I&amp;rsquo;m the one who helps unlock all this.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Do you feel like there are a thousand problems in your company?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Maybe you think everything needs to be changed: processes, roles, sales, even company culture.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Technologies used to build this site</title><link>https://matteocervelli.com/en/tech-stack/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:12:52 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://matteocervelli.com/en/tech-stack/</guid><description>&lt;p>Updated: 2025-01-17&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This website was created by Matteo Cervelli using a mix of personal skills and AI. I previously had a website hosted and built on WordPress, but I decided to rebuild it myself in early 2025 to &amp;ldquo;keep control&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I wanted a lightweight, fast, and responsive website. And I wanted to learn the basics by leveraging what technology has to offer.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>First of all, matteocervelli.com is a static website. It&amp;rsquo;s built with &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io">Hugo&lt;/a> as SSG—Static Site Generator—and is hosted on &lt;a href="https://www.netlify.com">Netlify&lt;/a> via &lt;a href="https://github.com">GitHub&lt;/a>, while DNS is managed through &lt;a href="https://www.cloudflare.com">Cloudflare&lt;/a>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What I'm doing now</title><link>https://matteocervelli.com/en/now/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:12:52 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://matteocervelli.com/en/now/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>Note: this is a &lt;a href="https://nownownow.com">Now&lt;/a> page.&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Updated: 2025-01-18, from my home in Poggibonsi, Tuscany, Italy.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="i-help-companies-grow-in-a-scalable-way">I help companies grow in a scalable way&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>I am a business consultant and advisor.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My work consists of helping companies grow in a scalable way through Strategy, Change Management, Sales and Business Development, Leadership Training and Coaching.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Many of my entrepreneur friends have noticed that I&amp;rsquo;ve switched to the other side of the fence. My strength lies precisely in combining my experience as a family business partner + medium/large company management + international sales with my skills as a Scalability Engineer.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://matteocervelli.com/en/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:26:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://matteocervelli.com/en/about/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="in-short">In short&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m Matteo Cervelli. I am &lt;a href="https://matteocervelli.com/work/business-scalability-engineer">Business Scalability Engineer&lt;/a>. I act as a &lt;a href="https://matteocervelli.com/en/work/">Consultant and Advisor&lt;/a>. Previously I managed &lt;a href="https://www.urania.group">Urania Group&lt;/a> as Co-CEO.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Today I help entrepreneurs and leaders to grow their business, in strategy, management, sales, implementing the principles of scalability.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My purpose is to trigger people to build a more beautiful world, together.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I am a father of 3 little girls, Emma, ​​Maria and Emma, ​​and two dogs: Maple and Cookie. Even before that, I am a husband: Sara and I have known each other since 2005 and in these 20 years we have loved each other and have always been there for each other, one, two and infinite.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Testimonials</title><link>https://matteocervelli.com/en/testimonials/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://matteocervelli.com/en/testimonials/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="what-people-say-about-working-with-me">What People Say About Working With Me&lt;/h2>
&lt;div class="testimonials-filters">
 &lt;div class="filter-group">
 &lt;label for="industry-filter">Industry:&lt;/label>
 &lt;select id="industry-filter">
 &lt;option value="all">All Industries&lt;/option>
 &lt;/select>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;div class="filter-group">
 &lt;label for="keyword-search">Search:&lt;/label>
 &lt;input type="text" id="keyword-search" placeholder="Search testimonials...">
 &lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;div class="testimonials-grid" id="testimonials-container">
 &lt;!-- Testimonials will be loaded here -->
&lt;/div></description></item></channel></rss>