<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Work on Matteo Cervelli</title><link>https://matteocervelli.com/en/categories/work/</link><description>Recent content in Work on Matteo Cervelli</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 12:53:02 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matteocervelli.com/en/categories/work/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss"/><item><title>Work with me</title><link>https://matteocervelli.com/en/work/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 14:52:50 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://matteocervelli.com/en/work/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="my-value-system">My value system&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="why">Why&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>I unlock people&amp;rsquo;s talent and potential to build a more beautiful world together.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="how">How&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>I help companies grow in a scalable way, to build ecosystems that enable comfort, skills, and overall well-being.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what">What&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>I work as a consultant, advisor, and trainer, as well as making personal investments.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="principles">Principles&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Beauty&lt;/strong> is the key to unleashing creativity and eliminating poverty.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Whether you choose easy or difficult &lt;strong>challenges&lt;/strong>, they require the same energy. Always aim high.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Learning, &lt;strong>failing&lt;/strong>, and trying again are the only ways to grow.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A company&amp;rsquo;s capability is its unique value proposition, its potential lies in the strength of &lt;strong>relationships&lt;/strong> that leadership maintains.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>An evolving business is based on few &lt;strong>experiments&lt;/strong>, but with great potential. And at the same time, many diversified stimuli of mammoth opportunities that simmer quietly.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;a href="#book-now" class="mc-button" id="book-now-button" data-umami-event="Book Now Button Click 1">
 Book now a free session
 &lt;br>
 to talk about your idea
&lt;/a>
&lt;h2 id="services-i-offer">Services I offer&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="management-consulting">Management Consulting&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>My consulting services are customized to &lt;a href="https://matteocervelli.com/en/business-scalability-engineer">unlock your company&amp;rsquo;s potential&lt;/a> and guide you toward success. Working together, we&amp;rsquo;ll transform challenges into opportunities. I can support you with tailored methodologies, strategic vision, insights, and operational excellence.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Unlock your business growth with a Scalability Engineer</title><link>https://matteocervelli.com/en/business-scalability-engineer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 08:41:33 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://matteocervelli.com/en/business-scalability-engineer/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="here-is-why-you-need-a-business-scalability-engineer-to-grow-your-business-the-way-it-deserves">Here is why you need a Business Scalability Engineer to grow your business the way it deserves.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Do you know when a company seems blocked, growth slows down, problems multiply and you don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start to put things back in order?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Here, I&amp;rsquo;m the one who helps unlock all this.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Do you feel like there are a thousand problems in your company?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Maybe you think everything needs to be changed: processes, roles, sales, even company culture.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>