<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scalability on Matteo Cervelli</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/tags/scalability/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scalability on Matteo Cervelli</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 07:46:49 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localhost:1313/en/tags/scalability/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Revenue: 5 KPIs that Predict Your Scaling Capability</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/5-kpi-scalability/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 07:46:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/5-kpi-scalability/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you driving your company looking only at the rearview mirror?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Revenue tells you where you have been, not where you are going. Healthy and sustainable companies in the long term monitor indicators that can predict opportunities and risks. Leaders know that long-term success requires a complete vision beyond sales numbers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you want to know which are the key indicators that forward-thinking entrepreneurs monitor?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this article I will show you the dashboard of indicators to constantly update that make the difference between a resilient business and one vulnerable to unforeseen events.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Predict Your Company&#39;s Growth Potential (Before It&#39;s Too Late)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/newsletter/predicting-growth-potential/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 07:46:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/newsletter/predicting-growth-potential/</guid>
      <description>Discover the 5 predictive KPIs that reveal your company&amp;rsquo;s true ability to scale sustainably, moving beyond simple revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 3 Fundamental Pillars for Your Business Scalability</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/newsletter/3-pillars-scalability/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/newsletter/3-pillars-scalability/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to build a scalable business model by focusing on People, Processes, and Technology, inspired by Brunello Cucinelli&amp;rsquo;s success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 3 Pillars of Scalability: The Essential Elements for a Successful Business</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/3-pillars-of-scalability/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/3-pillars-of-scalability/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;150-grams&#34;&gt;150 grams&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you know why cashmere costs so much? Because the raw material is rare. Cashmere production is based on the wool produced by the so-called common goat, the Capra hircus, the classic white goat, considered one of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_the_world%27s_100_worst_invasive_species&#34;&gt;100 most invasive species in the world&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;150 grams is the amount of cashmere a goat produces in a year. In fact, cashmere is obtained by combing the goat&amp;rsquo;s neck, not shearing. And to produce cashmere, the goat must live in very cold regions, which develop secondary follicles creating this undercoat from which the wool is derived. Hand-combed, cared for, and prepared through a very labor-intensive process.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock your business growth with a Scalability Engineer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/business-scalability-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 08:41:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/business-scalability-engineer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;here-is-why-you-need-a-business-scalability-engineer-to-grow-your-business-the-way-it-deserves&#34;&gt;Here is why you need a Business Scalability Engineer to grow your business the way it deserves&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you know when a company seems blocked, growth slows down, problems multiply and you don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start to put things back in order?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here, I&amp;rsquo;m the one who helps unlock all this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you feel like there are a thousand problems in your company?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe you think everything needs to be changed: processes, roles, sales, even company culture.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tightrope Walker Manager: Mastering Leadership&#39;s Balancing Act</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/tightrope-walker-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/tightrope-walker-manager/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It takes 20 years to build a new manager. 20 years where those responsible for delegating constantly oscillate on the edge of anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-risk-behind-delegation&#34;&gt;The risk behind delegation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like tightrope walkers, managers swing between the fear of being surpassed by people who might have something more than them and the risk that their team will lose drive and, ultimately, competitiveness by relying on inadequate people. Leaders who take the path of delegation risk falling painfully. But those who make it and get to the end receive applause from the audience—the same audience that lives in constant expectation of the fatal misstep.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss> 