<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scalability on Matteo Cervelli</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/tags/scalability/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scalability on Matteo Cervelli</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 08:41:33 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localhost:1313/en/tags/scalability/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unlock your business growth with a Scalability Engineer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/business-scalability-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 08:41:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/business-scalability-engineer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;here-is-why-you-need-a-business-scalability-engineer-to-grow-your-business-the-way-it-deserves&#34;&gt;Here is why you need a Business Scalability Engineer to grow your business the way it deserves&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you know when a company seems blocked, growth slows down, problems multiply and you don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start to put things back in order?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here, I&amp;rsquo;m the one who helps unlock all this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you feel like there are a thousand problems in your company?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe you think everything needs to be changed: processes, roles, sales, even company culture.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tightrope Walker Manager: Mastering Leadership&#39;s Balancing Act</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/tightrope-walker-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/tightrope-walker-manager/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It takes 20 years to build a new manager. 20 years where those responsible for delegating constantly oscillate on the edge of anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-risk-behind-delegation&#34;&gt;The risk behind delegation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like tightrope walkers, managers swing between the fear of being surpassed by people who might have something more than them and the risk that their team will lose drive and, ultimately, competitiveness by relying on inadequate people. Leaders who take the path of delegation risk falling painfully. But those who make it and get to the end receive applause from the audience—the same audience that lives in constant expectation of the fatal misstep.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss> 